this is the b-2 spirit designed as the tip of
这是设计为尖端的b-2精神
the spear in strategic bombing operations
战略轰炸行动中的矛
it is a deep penetration bomber intended to pave the
这是一架深渗透轰炸机，旨在为
way for the b-1 lancer and ultimately for the massive
B-1枪骑兵的方式，最终为巨大的
cold war era bomber the boeing b-52 stratofortress
冷战时期的轰炸机波音b-52同温层堡垒
the b 2 spirit achieves its mission thanks to its
b2精神实现了它的使命
unique wing structure which deflects radar while the
独特的机翼结构，使雷达偏转
paint absorbs the remaining Radar signals rather
油漆吸收了剩下的雷达信号
than deflecting them back to their source
而不是让他们回到源头
enhancing its stealth capabilities
增强其隐身能力
to break it down further
进一步分解它
the aircraft is constructed from a
这架飞机是由
combination of materials Titanium
材料组合钛
graphite epoxy  fiberglass  polyimide
石墨环氧玻璃纤维聚酰亚胺
graphite polyimide and fiberglass epoxy
石墨聚酰亚胺和玻璃纤维环氧树脂
particularly on the leading edge and wingtips  however
尤其是前缘和翼尖
don't be deceived by its seemingly soft outer skin
不要被它看似柔软的外皮所欺骗
beneath the surface lies a robust framework of
表面之下是一个强大的框架
high strength steel ribs that allow the wings to
高强度钢肋，使机翼能够
flex and bend as needed during flight
在飞行过程中根据需要弯曲
to further maintain its stealth
以进一步保持其隐身性
profile and reduce its heat signature
剖面并减少其热信号
the engines are buried deep within the aircraft's body
引擎深埋在机体内部
they draw air from the front and
他们从前面吸入空气
expel only slightly warm air
排出微热的空气
which prevents these heat seeking missiles from locking
防止这些热追踪导弹锁定
onto the aircraft due to its minimal thermal signature
由于其最小的热信号
after three decades the us has sanctioned the newly
三十年后，美国批准了新的
developed b twenty one raider is significantly smaller
发达的b 21突袭机明显更小
when placed side by side along with an average
当与平均值并排放置时
human we can can notice the difference in size
人类，我们可以注意到大小的差异
the new b twenty one raider is expected to
新的b21突袭机预计将
utilize advanced stealth technologies to
利用先进的隐形技术
further reduce its Radar cross section
进一步缩小它的雷达横截面
increasing its survivability
提高它的生存能力
against modern air defense systems
对抗现代防空系统
moving to the b two spirit's cockpit is compact with
移动到b 2幽灵的驾驶舱是紧凑的
the commander and pilot seated side by side
指挥官和飞行员并排坐着
interestingly
有趣的是
the aircraft is equipped with ejection seats
飞机装有弹射座椅
when in an emergency
在紧急情况下
the protective covers pop open to allow the crew to safely
保护套弹出打开，让船员安全
evacuate the one billion dollars aircraft if necessary
如果有必要就疏散十亿美元的飞机
inside the Cockpit
驾驶舱内
advanced Avionics Systems are present
先进的航空电子系统
these include a fuel control system
其中包括燃料控制系统
an attitude display unit
姿态显示单元
the weapon control systems
武器控制系统
and a Terrain following Radar  together
和地形跟踪雷达一起
these technologies enable the pilot and
这些技术使试点和
copilot to navigate and operate the aircraft
副驾驶驾驶飞机
even in darkness or regions with blind spots
即使在黑暗或有盲点的区域
speaking of blind spots
说到盲点
you can also look for sources using this tool
您也可以使用此工具查找来源
here for hidden news not seen on the internet
这里有互联网上看不到的隐藏新闻
you can get more than one thousand digital news
您可以获得一千多条数字新闻
outlets and will demonstrate how misinformation
并将展示虚假信息
media bias shape the coverage of news like this one
媒体偏见影响了这类新闻的报道
Israel signs five point two billion dollars deal to
以色列签署52亿美元协议
acquire twenty five f fifteen fighter jets from Boeing
从波音公司购买25架f 15战斗机
ground news reports that sixty eight
地面新闻报道68
sources are covering this story
消息来源正在报道这个故事
six lean left
左倾六
nine on the center and eleven leaning right
中间9个，右边11个
they also have a bias distribution
它们也有偏差分布
tool to help visualize this
帮助可视化的工具
just below you'll find the factuality rating
就在下面，你会发现事实评级
to ensure the credibility of the sources
确保消息来源的可信度
we can also look at who owns these news outlets
我们还可以看看谁拥有这些新闻媒体
here thirty eight percent of the sources
这里有38%的来源
are owned by media conglomerates
都归传媒集团所有
on the left
在左边
nation of change frames the sentence as
改变的国家将句子框定为
Israel bombs Gaza refugee camps following
以色列轰炸加沙难民营
the five point two billion dollars deal
52亿美元的交易
and finally on the right
最后在右边
first post news reports seven key features of f fifteen
First post news报道了f15的七个主要特点
fighter jets that Israel has decided to buy from us
以色列决定从我们这里购买战斗机
this comparison shows how framing
这种比较显示了框架
impacts perceptions in news
影响新闻中的感知
ground news is offering my viewers fifty
地面新闻给我的观众出价50美元
percent off their unlimited access vantage plan
无限制访问优势计划的八折优惠
use my link or scan the QR code here for the best deal
使用我的链接或扫描这里的二维码以获得最佳交易
we will also look into the split rudder system
我们还将研究分开的方向舵系统
along with the secret stealth paint material
还有秘密的隐形涂料材料
composition all in the video ahead
构图都在前面的视频中
a little history about the b-2 spirit dates back to the
B-2幽灵的历史可以追溯到
designs of revolutionary engineer jack northrop
革命性工程师杰克诺斯罗普的设计
who invented the flying wing aircraft
谁发明了飞翼飞机
this design was first introduced in the year
这种设计是在今年首次推出的
nineteen forty nine as the yb forty nine
1949作为yb 49
unfortunately
不幸的是
it was rejected at the time
当时被拒收了
but northrop's fly by wire technology laid the
但诺斯罗普的电传技术奠定了
foundation for advances in stability systems
稳定系统进步的基础
these systems allow inherently unstable aircraft like the
这些系统允许固有的不稳定飞机，如
b two spirit to be flown like conventional aircraft
b两个精神像传统飞机一样飞行
let's take a look inside the b two spirit frame structure
让我们看看b两个精神框架结构的内部
at the front is the composite wing tip
前面是复合材料翼尖
this section comprises the ribs of
此部分包括肋骨
the outer part of the wing
翼的外部部分
both integral fuel tanks can hold approximately
两个整体燃料箱大约可以容纳
one hundred and sixty seven thousand pounds
十六万七千英镑
which translates to about seventy
这相当于大约七十
five thousand kilograms of fuel
五千公斤燃料
which is a significant amount
这是一个很大的数量。
just a small comparison
只是一个小小的比较
this aircraft's fuel reserve can fill up two tanker trucks
这架飞机的燃料储备可以装满两辆油罐车
making it an insanely gas guzzling machine
使它成为一个疯狂耗油的机器
moving further back there is
向后移动更远的地方
another section of the fuel tank
油箱的另一部分
these fuel tanks were specifically designed to penetrate
这些油箱是专门设计用于穿透
deep into Russian territory about six thousand nine hundred
深入俄国领土大约六千九百
miles which is around eleven thousand kilometers
英里，大约一万一千公里。
furthermore it can travel double that distance
此外，它可以移动两倍的距离
deep into enemy lines while avoiding radar
深入敌阵同时躲避雷达
detection thanks to this rotary air refueling
由于这种旋转空中加油，检测
system that extends all the way out as shown here
如图所示，一直延伸到外面的系统
this maximizes its range to twelve thousand miles with
这使它的射程最大化到一万二千英里
the Boeing KC one three five strato tanker and allows
波音KC一三五斯特拉托加油机并允许
it to remain airborne for forty four hours
它将在空中停留44小时
that is almost two days in the air
那已经快两天了
which is a remarkable engineering feat
这是一项了不起的工程壮举
all that fuel are consumed by these four general
所有的燃料都被这四个将军消耗掉了
electric f one one eight turbofan engines
电动f一一八涡扇发动机
each with seventeen thousand
每人一万七千
three hundred pounds of thrust
三百磅的推力
let's take a look from the side profile
让我们从侧面剖面看一下
as you can see
如你所见
it has its engine buried deep in the
它的引擎深埋在
airframe with an s curve in front and behind
前后有s曲线的机身
this is how it reduces its heat signature
这就是它减少热信号的方式
air is sucked by the fan rotor as it draws in
空气被风扇转子吸入
which undergoes powerful compression in both the
在两个方面都经历了强大的压缩
low pressure and high pressure compressors
低压和高压压缩机
as the air enters the combustor
当空气进入燃烧室
this is where fuel injection occurs
这是燃油喷射发生的地方
this process generates a continuous combustion of
这个过程会产生持续的燃烧
fuel and air reaching temperatures of more or
燃料和空气温度达到
less than of one thousand degrees Celsius
不到一千摄氏度
the resultant heat causes the gas to expand
产生的热量使气体膨胀
leading it to escape from the combustor with high energy
导致它高能逃出燃烧室
flowing through both the high and low pressure turbines
流经高压和低压涡轮机
as a consequence
结果
the turbine blades rotate
涡轮叶片旋转
the energy liberated by this process
这个过程释放的能量
drives both the compressor and the fan
驱动压缩机和风扇
thus producing thrust
从而产生推力
just a reminder the b two spirit does not use afterburner
只是提醒一下，b 2精神不使用加力燃烧室
because as a stealth bomber it has to compromise on speed to
因为作为隐形轰炸机，它必须在速度上妥协
lower its heat signature the exhaust from the engines is
降低它的热信号引擎排出的废气
mixed with ambient air before it exits the airframe
在它离开机身前与周围空气混合
this significantly lowers the temperature of the exhaust
这大大降低了排气的温度
hence reducing the heat signature suitable for the stealth
因此减少了适合隐形的热信号
bomber to remain undetected as much as possible
轰炸机尽可能不被发现
for a conventional aircraft
对于传统飞机
it has ailerons at each wing tip that move
它的每个翼尖都有副翼可以移动
opposite one another to roll the plane
相对于另一个来滚动飞机
it also has elevators at the tail that affect pitch
它的尾部也有升降器，可以影响音高。
and the rudder controls yaw or rotation
方向舵控制偏航或旋转
however if we look at the b two spirit it doesn't have
然而，如果我们看看b 2精神，它没有
all of those control surfaces like a standard aircraft
所有这些控制面就像一架标准飞机
you'll notice that there are no leading edge slats the
你会注意到没有前缘板条
massive wing which essentially comprises the entire
巨大的翅膀，基本上包括整个
aircraft generates enough lift on its own
飞机自己产生足够的升力
instead the b two spirit has outboard elevons
取而代之的是b 2幽灵有舷外升降舵
located here close to the split drag rudder
位于这里靠近分裂的阻力舵
mid elevons and inboard elevons near the engine exhaust
中升降舵和内侧升降舵靠近发动机排气口
these control surfaces are located all over this
这些控制面都在这个上面。
area and move independently as a single unit
区域并作为一个单元独立移动
they can move opposite one another to achieve
它们可以相对移动以实现
roll and work together for pitch control
滚动并一起工作以控制音高
they also use a combination of both for maneuvers
它们也结合使用两者进行机动
that require some roll and pitch at the same time
同时需要一些滚动和俯仰
as stated almost every aircraft has a rudder
如前所述，几乎每架飞机都有方向舵
and elevators to turn and stabilize the plane
和电梯来转动和稳定飞机
but the b two spirit has none of these
但是b二精神这些都没有
this is because any vertical
这是因为任何垂直的
structure would reflect radar waves
结构会反射雷达波
which is why they had to design it without
这就是为什么他们必须在没有
vertical stabilizer or rudder at the rear
后部的垂直稳定器或方向舵
instead they use this technique of split drag
相反，他们使用这种分裂阻力技术
rudders to provide directional stability and
方向舵提供方向稳定性和
control in a flying wing aircraft
飞翼飞机的控制
but there is a catch
但有一个陷阱
as opposed to conventional rudders
与传统方向舵相反
the control efficiency of split drag rudders is
分体式阻力舵的控制效率为
typically low for small deflection angles
对于小偏转角度通常很低
that is why the b-2 spirit turns very
这就是为什么B-2精神变得非常
slowly compared to other military planes
与其他军用飞机相比很慢
each split rudder consists of two separate panels
每个分开的方向舵由两个独立的面板组成
that swing out vertically in opposite directions
以相反的方向垂直摆动
when the left split rudder opens
当左分舵打开时
it produces drag and causes the b-2 spirit to yaw to
它产生阻力并导致B-2幽灵偏航
the left in the direction of the open split rudder
开叉舵方向的左边
the same effect occurs with the
同样的效果发生在
opposing right side split rudder
对侧右分舵
this is what happens inside the cockpit when
这就是驾驶舱内发生的事情
the pilot pushes the left rudder pedal
飞行员推动左舵踏板
the left split rudder opens
左分开舵打开
causing the aircraft to yaw to the left  similarly
导致飞机同样向左偏航
when the pilot pushes the right rudder pedal
当飞行员按下右舵踏板时
the right split rudder opens
右分舵打开
causing the aircraft to yaw to the right
导致飞机向右偏航
the b two spirit composite can be
b两个精神复合材料可以是
divided into several parts  here
在这里分成几个部分
we find that all the edges are made of
我们发现所有的边缘都是由
fiberglass epoxy to reflect radar
反射雷达的玻璃纤维环氧树脂
while the largest part of the wing is
而翅膀最大的部分是
primarily made of graphite epoxy
主要由石墨环氧树脂制成
interestingly
有趣的是
the crew station assembly is made up of aluminum
乘员站总成是铝制的
at the base  since these areas have to withstand
在基地，因为这些区域必须承受
a lot of heat from the engine
发动机产生大量热量
they are made of Titanium
它们是钛做的
a super strong
超级强者
expensive material
昂贵的材料
finally  we have fiberglass polyamide
最后是玻璃纤维聚酰胺
a stealthy material able to withstand heat
一种能够耐热的隐形材料
this is what it looks like with all the labeling and
这就是所有标签和
segments assigned to it to give you a better picture
分配给它的段，以便为您提供更好的图片
let's take a look at the one billion dollars Radar
让我们来看看十亿美元的雷达
paint technology which is still classified
仍属机密的油漆技术
but here's what we know from aviation experts
但我们从航空专家那里了解到
it involves the use of Radar
它涉及到雷达的使用
absorbing material also called ram
吸收材料也称为ram
RAM is a polymer based material applied to the
RAM是一种聚合物基材料，应用于
surface of stealth military aircraft like the f
像f这样的隐形军用飞机的表面
twenty two raptor and f thirty five Lightning II
22猛禽和f 35闪电II
moving to the belly of the beast and opening
移动到野兽的腹部并打开
the bomb bay door is this weapon adapter
炸弹舱门是这个武器适配器
suspension which makes this bomber formidable
悬架让这架轰炸机变得强大
while the b 2 spirit might look small
而b2精神可能看起来很小
it can fit around eighty numbers of mark
它可以容纳大约八十个标记
eighty two bombs weighing five hundred pounds
八十二枚炸弹重五百磅
yes  all these eighty weapons can fit
是的这八十把武器都能装下
inside this weapon adapter
在这个武器适配器里面
totaling around forty thousand pounds
总计约四万英镑
which is approximately eighteen thousand
大约是一万八千
kilograms of free fall gravity weapon system
千克的自由落体重力武器系统
depending on the mission
取决于任务
the b two spirit can switch to this rotary weapon system
b二精灵可以切换到这个旋转武器系统
enabling it to carry around sixteen
使它能够携带大约16个
numbers of agm one five eight missiles
AGM一五八导弹的数量
which can cost around one point five million dollars each
每台大约要花费150万美元
when ready the b two spirit can drop
准备好后，b 2精神可以下降
this weapon payload discreetly
这个武器的有效载荷要小心
the agm missiles unfold their
AGM导弹展开
wings to fly towards the target
飞向目标的翅膀
traveling up to two hundred and thirty miles
行进了二百三十英里
which is around three hundred and seventy kilometers
大约三百七十公里
let's take a look at how this works  step one
让我们看看第一步是如何工作的
the bomb deployment platform
炸弹部署平台
as previously mentioned
如前所述
a b two stealth bomber flies in a very high altitude
a b 2隐形轰炸机在高空飞行
when the aircraft reaches the designated
当飞机到达指定
location and the conditions are optimal
位置和条件是最佳的
it can release this specialized moab weapon system
它可以释放这种特殊的摩押武器系统
the bomb is designed for precision
炸弹是为精确而设计的
and the deployment height plays a crucial
部署高度起着至关重要的作用
role in its trajectory and effectiveness
在其轨迹和有效性中的作用
then step two comes the targeting precision
然后第二步是瞄准精度
the bomb is outfitted with advanced guidance
炸弹配备了先进的制导装置
technology including gps and inertial navigation
包括gps和惯性导航在内的技术
systems which are military grade satellites
军用级卫星系统
then comes step three that is adjusting the trajectory
然后是第三步，调整轨迹
the guidance information and data is then transmitted to
然后将引导信息和数据传输到
the bomb's four lattice motors fins located at the rear
炸弹的四个格子发动机鳍位于后部
these fins can move and adjust in real time
这些鳍可以实时移动和调整
allowing the bomb to correct its course as
让炸弹改道
it descends under the force of gravity
它在重力的作用下下降
these adjustments are essential because the weapon
这些调整是必不可少的，因为武器
does not have thrusters to change its trajectory  instead
没有推进器来改变它的轨迹
it relies on the movement of these fins and the
它依赖于这些鳍的运动和
high altitude drop to control its flight path
高空下降以控制其飞行路径
this is why the bomb must be deployed from a
这就是为什么炸弹必须从一个
very high altitude so it has enough time and
非常高的海拔，所以它有足够的时间和
distance to adjust its trajectory accurately
精确调整其轨迹的距离
here comes the most difficult part that
最困难的部分来了
is step four impact and penetration
是第四步冲击和渗透
the bomb known as the massive ordnance penetrator
被称为大规模军械穿透器的炸弹
weighs approximately thirty thousand pounds
重约三万磅
which is around fourteen thousand kilograms
大约一万四千公斤
when it reaches its target it strikes with
当它到达目标时
immense force designed to penetrate deep into
巨大的力量旨在深入
hardened structures such as bunkers
坚硬的结构，如掩体
the energy upon impact allows the bomb to bury itself
撞击时的能量让炸弹自行掩埋
over two hundred feet into reinforced concrete
深入钢筋混凝土200多英尺
ensuring it delivers its payload precisely
确保它能精确地发射有效载荷
where it is intended for maximum effect
旨在达到最大效果的地方
but why do we need the b two bomber when we
但是为什么我们需要b 2轰炸机，当我们
have the b fifty two strato fortress animated
让b 52斯特拉托堡垒动画化
in our recent video and the b one lancer
在我们最近的视频和b one枪骑兵中
let's take a look at how this works
让我们来看看这是如何工作的
the first line of attack involves the b two stealth bomber
第一道攻击线涉及b 2隐形轰炸机
moving in to destroy high value air defense systems like the
进入摧毁高价值的防空系统
famous s 400 triumph and other surface to air missiles
著名的s 400凯旋和其他地对空导弹
effectively disabling them by using its stealth technology
通过使用其隐形技术有效地禁用它们
next
下一个
the b one lancer flies at a very low altitude towards enemy
B-1枪骑兵以极低的高度飞向敌人
targets to take out older anti aircraft guns and missiles
目标是摧毁老式高射炮和导弹
this clears the way for conventional
这为传统扫清了道路
aircraft like the b fifty two stratofortress
像b 52层堡垒这样的飞机
which can then sweep in to destroy any critical
然后可以横扫进去摧毁任何关键的
infrastructure without facing anti aircraft threats
没有防空威胁的基础设施
this is the reason they need both the b 2 stealth
这就是他们需要B2隐形飞机的原因
bomber and conventional bombers as there are only
轰炸机和常规轰炸机
nineteen units of the b 2 spirit in service to date
迄今为止服役的19架b 2烈酒
we also make original engineering content
我们还制作原创工程内容
so please subscribe and hit the
所以请订阅并点击
notification bell for more videos
更多视频的通知铃